pics.io 2019-05-19

# Pics.io | Privacy Policy

## About this policy

This is the Privacy Policy for TopTechPhoto inc ("Group" or "us" or "we" or "our"), where we are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy (together with our Terms of Service and any other documents referred to in it) explains how we collect and use any personal data you provide to us or which we collect from you and how we process such data. Please read this privacy policy carefully as by accessing and/or using our services, you are deemed to accept and consent to the terms of this privacy policy and the practices described in it.

Please feel free to contact us at [support@pics.io](mailto:support@pics.io) if you have any questions regarding this policy, your personal data processing or any other issues about our services.

## About us

We are a company registered in the United States of America, state Delaware. Our office is at 641 Lexington Avenue, 14th Floor, New York, New York 10022. For details on how to contact us, please refer to our Contact section. Alternatively, you can forward an email to [support@toptechphoto.com.](mailto:support@toptechphoto.com.)

## How we collect information from you

We may collect and process information that you give us. You may give us information about you by filling in any forms, surveys etc. on our site or by corresponding with us by phone, email or otherwise. This may include information you provide when you subscribe, register, enter a promotional activity, sign up for an alert, complete a survey, or participate in any discussions or other social media activities, make enquiries, provide feedback or report a problem with our site. We may also collect information if you contact us offline, e.g. by telephone, fax or post. The information you give us may include your name, address, email address, and phone number. We may collect anonymous information about you when you visit our site through the use of various technologies including the use of 'cookies' and 'web beacons' which may include technical information, such as :

  * the Internet Protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet, any login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
  * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including data and time), items you searched for, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page, and any phone numbers used to call our contact number.

## How we use your information

We use information held about you for technical purposes, such as functioning of our services and marketing purposes if you agree to register with us. From time to time, we may use your information to contact you with details about our products and services which we feel may be of interest to you. We may also use and analyze the information that we collect in order to administer, support, improve and develop our site. If you do not want the information we hold on you to be used in these ways, you must contact us by emailing us at support@pics.io and establishing your preferences. You can also review, download or request the deletion of your personal information right from the user interface of our products. You can find this functionality on your account page.

## Personal information and content

Personal Information means information that by itself explicitly identifies an individual (such as name, email address, photo, links to other resources) or that can be combined with other information to identify an individual.

If we hold any personal information about you which is incorrect or if there are any changes to your details, please let us know so that we can keep our records accurate and up to date.

We will delete all your personal data 3 years after your last interaction with our service. The period of storing personal data is determined by the respective statutory retention period. After this period expires, the corresponding data is routinely deleted, as long as it is no longer necessary for the fulfillment of the contract or the initiation of a contract. Please note that you have the right to delete your personal information from our service or restrict the processing of your personal information by our staff and our subcontractors. You need to contact us at [support@pics.io](mailto:support@pics.io) or use the tools available on your account page to delete the data or restrict the data processing.

## Security and storage information

We will keep your information secure by taking appropriate technical and organisational measures against its unauthorized or unlawful processing and against its accidental loss, destruction or damage. Please remember that the internet and email are not always secure and whilst we will always do our best to protect your information, we cannot guarantee that your information will remain secure, so if you transmit any information via our site or email any information to us, you do it at your own risk. If we have given you or if you have chosen a password to certain services, please keep your password safe. We will not share this password with anyone either.

TopTechPhoto inc. will not view, access or use your Content, including your Personal Information, except if it is needed to actually deliver our Products in the framework of Product support authorized by the Customer. In the course of providing Product support requested by the Customer, TopTechPhoto inc. may have incidental access to Content. Any Customer request for Product support will be deemed as a permission for us to access particular Content for the limited purposes of providing the requested Product support. Customer, as the data controller, is responsible for furnishing any notices or obtaining any consents required by law from the relevant individuals.

Personal Information, including your Content, does not include Aggregate Information, which is information we collect or process about a group or category of data. Aggregate Information cannot be attributed to any individual. We may use and share such Aggregate Information to improve Products, develop new products, understand and/or analyze usage, demand, and general industry trends, develop and publish white papers, reports, and databases summarizing the foregoing, and generally for any purpose related to our business. Aggregate Information may be derived from the information provided by any Customer, from the use of our Products or from passive data collection techniques described below. No Personal Information is included in Aggregate Information.

All data stored by us is only used for internal processing and is never sold or otherwise given away. In addition to that, we use the following third party services which also store data about you:

  1. Amazon Web Services (for data)
  2. Google Cloud (for data)
  3. Google Analytics (for statistics)
  4. Stripe.com (for payments)
  5. Intercom.com (for customer support service)
  6. Amplitude.com (for statistics)
  7. Appcues.com (for users onboarding)

## Accessing your information on third party resources

Some of TopTechPhoto inc. products or services may need to access your information stored on third party services, such as Google Drive, DropBox, Amazon S3, etc. The access to the information is always limited to the scope of the product or the service. Our services always access data or content within a specific scope, such as folders, buckets, collections, etc. The scope of access is a subject of consent accepted by a user during the user initiation. No information from third party services will be published, viewed or accessed in any other way without the user’s explicit action.

## Information you share

TopTechPhoto inc. services let you share information with others. Remember that when you share information publicly, it may be indexable by search engines. Our services provide you with different options for sharing and removing your content.

## Other sites

If you follow a link from our site to another third party website, this policy will no longer apply. We are not responsible for how other websites handle your information and we encourage you to read the privacy policies appearing on those websites. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for such third party websites and you use such third party websites at your own risk.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may change and update our Privacy Policy from time to time, so please try to read it frequently to see any updates or changes. This Privacy Policy was last updated on 25 May 2018. Thank you for visiting our site.
